We're here to talk.
You make a move against Eamon?
Of course not. I don't know
anything about this shit.
Eamon Sweeney is
not to be touched.
Or anyone in my crew.
Do we go after Gotti?
No. I got a better way
to get that motherfucker back.
He's not allowed
to sell drugs so we will.
Well. right on.
Your pal Leon's dead.
Turns out Charlie Bricks was
in Gotti's pocket
the whole fuckin' time.
This is
Tadhg McKenna's daughter.
She's currently called
Bridget Walsh because
of the Interpol warrant
for the bombings
of the London Tube.
What I was doing wasn't
just for Ireland.
It was for you.
My target. the British operative
Colonel Gerald Markham.
The man who killed your parents.
We're gonna blow
this motherfucker
-to smithereens.
-A car bomb?
So. there is gonna be
civilian casualties.
This is a war. Bridget.
Or have you forgotten that?
You've been pretty
fuckin' useless.
Does this mean
I'm getting fired?
It means you're
gonna wear a wire.
Who's his most trusted man?
Toss up between Eddie Breen
and Dukey Sullivan.
Half-ass copper piece of shit.
Dukey is not a big fan
of the boys in blue.
You got wind Eddie was
gonna get grabbed up.
you didn't think
I might wanna know?
What have you done
that Breen knows about?
You can ask him yourself.
See. the problem is now.
Glenn. is I can't trust you.
Neither do I.
You fuckin' cunt.
So. we get this blow.
-And then what's the plan?
-We start selling.
You're offering us a job?
Well. I'm offering
you boys a future.
My supply. Your streets.
Fifty-fifty.
Hey. we ain't never selling
for that dago bastard. right?
Of course. we're fuckin' not.
They'll be back.
♪ Whoa... ooh ♪
♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
♪ No. no. no.
no. no. no. no ♪
♪ Well. we can't
take her this week ♪
♪ And her friends don't
want another speech ♪
♪ Hoping for her
that someday ♪
♪ They'll hear
what she's got to say ♪
Hey! Here he is!
Hey. everybody! It's the king
of Hell's Kitchen right here!
Jimmy. it's fucking line time.
No. it's not fucking
line time. all right?
-It's fuckin' line time!
-You take it easy on it.
all right?
Hey. Sean. here.
-I fucking love you. Jimmy.
-I fucking love you too.
-You want a shot?
-Of course I fucking do.
-Three shots. Ray.
-Yeah. comin' right up.
-Come on!
-Hey. I got you.
Three shots.
This is for me?
Are you doin' this for me?
Oh. you're too good!
Oh...
Hey. don't spend it
all at once. all right?
Oh! I fuckin' love you.
I fuckin' love you.
Hey. Jimmy. business is good.
but we're running low.
Yeah. I gotta speak
to Nelson again soon.
Those Dominicans will get us
whatever the fuck we want.
Slàinte.
Hey. in that case.
you want a bump?
I'm good.
Hey.
Keep up the good work.
All right?
Ray. for your troubles.
Bless you. Jimmy.
My rounds are done.
I can finally... relax.
As you deserve.
I've never seen
the boys this happy.
It's what they deserve.
It's real cash in their pockets.
Yeah. You did that.
It's nice seeing someone
be good to them. for once.
Now. What am I gonna buy you?
With this? Hmm?
What do you want? A new dress?
You don't like what I'm wearing?
Oh. no. no. no.
I like it just fine.
I just mean more dresses.
I thought you liked me
with less clothes on.
No. I don't need things.
Come on. everyone
needs something.
What do you need?
And don't make me sorry
I just asked that.
Can you give me peace of mind?
Give me that.
I could.
If you just let me in there.
No. sexual favors.
that'll do just fine.
Hey. here's our boy-o.
Jim! Jimmy.
Remember what I told you. right?
-Yeah.
-It's gonna be great. Jimmy!
It's Rad Tad. This is the guy
I was telling you about.
-Tad Guggenheim.
-Hey.
Heard a lot about you.
Uh. heard you can.
uh. get some good shit.
Yeah. so I. uh. I thought that
maybe we could do business.
You know. you and me.
What do you want?
Well. what do you think?
The good stuff. you know.
Pure stuff. Lots of it.
Where the fuck
did you guys meet?
At just. like.
parties and stuff.
He bought a couple bags
off me here and there.
But he's a good customer. Jimmy.
Fuckin' right I am.
And I'm about to be
your best customer. yeah?
'Cause I wanna buy a lot.
'cause I know people richer
than you could ever imagine.
Like millionaires
and billionaires.
And I'm gonna become
your middleman.
All right. all right.
just calm down.
Tad.
Go get yourself a drink or
something and. yeah. we'll talk.
Later.
Yeah. we'll talk.
Let's go get a beer.
What a douchebag.
Congratulations.
-♪ It didn't take long ♪
-♪ I didn't get far ♪
♪ Before the cops were told ♪
-♪ That I'd stolen the car ♪
-♪ Stolen the car ♪
-♪ There was an APB ♪
-♪ APB ♪
-♪ Sent out for me ♪
-♪ Out for me ♪
♪ Ratted out by my own ♪
♪ Now I'm a public enemy ♪
♪ I'm a Catholic school kid ♪
-♪ I'm an altar boy ♪
-♪ Altar boy ♪
♪ I was dropped on my head ♪
-♪ Now I'm here to destroy ♪
-♪ Here to destroy ♪
-♪ I'm a stone-cold killer ♪
-♪ Stone-cold killer ♪
-♪ In the CYO ♪
-♪ CYO ♪
♪ I'm lining them up ♪
♪ And I'm laying them low ♪
♪ But honest as the day
is long that's a fact ♪
♪ I'm not nearly half
as bad as I act ♪
♪ See. I'm always wrong
in the eyes of the law ♪
♪ Parents and priests say
it's the final straw ♪
♪ But sure as the sun.
it rises and sets ♪
♪ I'll do it again.
it's a surefire bet ♪
Yeah. my stepfather
is a Guggenheim.
total fucking asshole.
The thought of him porking
my mom makes me sick.
But the dude is a degenerate.
you know. and so is
all his friends.
Oh. degenerates. huh?
Well. you should have me
for dinner sometime.
Yeah. look. the point is
that his friends love coke.
and they're always
lookin' to buy.
And my friends from Yale too.
Oh. you went to Yale?
I told you he was fuckin' smart.
Yeah. For a few months.
and then. uh. then I left.
Yeah. I got kicked out.
I was...
I was fucking this chick
who was still in high school.
Yeah. I'm not interested
in your life story.
How much you want?
Well. since this is my first go.
uh...
why don't we start small?
Ten kilos?
Mickey. you recognize
this guy from Bellevue. maybe?
Hey. Good job.
You brought us a fuckin' retard.
Hey. asshole. you don't know
what the fuck
you're talking about.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I do.
Look. I've done my research.
See. my idea...
is to give
my rich fuckin' friends
a luxury fuckin' experience.
Like shit that's
not cut with anything.
Pure coke.
You understand
that as a general rule.
coke gets cut up
at each stage of distribution.
That's how you make money.
No. No. no. no. none of this
baby powder shit for me.
And I'll charge a premium price.
How much do you think
ten keys will cost you?
I have no fuckin' idea.
Two million dollars.
Seriously?
Oh. get him the fuck outta here!
Wait. no. I think
he might go for it.
Tad. tell him you can get
the fuckin' money.
-Well. two million dollars.
-Oh. c'mon. enough.
there's no way
on this fucking Earth
I'm getting you
ten keys of anything.
Now. you want coke?
One key. 100 grand.
All right. big shot?
A hundred grand?
-Okay.
-What?
You gonna ask
your step-daddy for a check?
I can get it. no problem.
Mickey. Mickey. c'mon.
Now. don't fuck with me.
You can get that kinda money?
Yeah.
No problem.
Okay? I'll be in touch.
How you feeling. Glenn?
Fine.
Three broken ribs is rough.
I broke one once as a kid.
fell off my bike.
Had a hard time
breathing for months.
Superficial fractures.
I'm ready to get back to work.
Finish what we started.
Let me speak plainly.
What I need is competent.
clear-thinking police work.
Not someone
hell-bent on revenge.
Look. I have my failings...
but I'm a professional.
You can count on that.
I think I can.
Yeah. look. I been thinkin'
about the case.
You want Sweeney
to flip on Castellano.
But right now
he's too protected.
You need someone who will cave.
Eddie Breen was the wrong mark.
Who's the right mark?
Dukey Sullivan.
Sweeney's other lieutenant.
If we have evidence.
You leave that to me.
But I can get Dukey to cave.
And once he does...
they'll all start folding.
We're going
to kill Colonel Markham
as he leaves the British
Consulate tomorrow.
So. here's how this goes.
The Semtex gets loaded carefully
into the boot.
or for the two Americans.
the trunk of the car.
Main charge sits low
on the gas tank.
We'll layer it.
Two kilos in total.
It'll peel the car open
like a sardine tin.
Donal. you explain the rest.
This is the blasting cap.
Czech-made. fast fuse.
Runs to this receiver.
What about the trigger?
We use this:
a garage door remote.
nothing fancy.
So you tune the receiver
to match the VHF frequency?
Yes. but you'll need
a clear line of sight.
It's not that strong.
Say. half a block away.
What if the signal gets blocked?
Then the garage doors
don't open.
That's not gonna happen.
I'll be less half a block
away from Markham.
Signal will be strong and clear.
Besides. I want the last thing
that bastard see
to be my grinnin' face.
I don't think
that's a good idea. Brendan.
Colonel Markham personally
interrogated you in Maze Prison.
I told you. I'm not gonna
go anywhere near him.
No. Someone else should do it.
It's plain and simple.
Oh. That someone else is you?
My whole family died
at Markham's hands.
Let him die at mine.
All right.
Nine. ten.
All right. That's another
thousand right there.
Wait. Is that it?
That's all of it?
That's it. Jimmy.
That's everything.
No. no. no. no. no.
We're short.
I mean. we're really
fucking short. Mickey.
-How is that possible?
-Well. 'cause unlike
the motherfucker
that you call boss.
who takes his fucking kickbacks
and keeps it all for himself.
you're actually generous
with your people.
Yeah. well. maybe I wouldn't
have been so fuckin' generous
if I knew that was
all we were gonna take.
-I know.
-Shit!
All right. well.
look. look. we're starting
a new business here.
This shit happens. right?
So maybe we're too generous
with too many people.
and maybe we had
a bit too much fun.
We know now. next time
we'll tighten it up.
Thing we do know is that
we can make real fuckin' money.
It's just... it's just...
it's overheads. right?
Fuckin' overheads.
Shit. we're not gonna have
enough for that key for Tad.
I mean. that knucklehead
was gonna spend
a hundred grand on one key.
That woulda been
a big fuckin' score. Mickey.
All right.
So. we take
Sweeney's fuckin' cut.
-and we use that for our blow.
-No. no. no. no. no. no. no.
We cannot fuckin' do that.
-Why not?
-You know why not.
Look. I'll talk to Sweeney.
and who knows?
Maybe he's feeling generous.
Yeah. right.
Not a bad day at the office.
Business has been
pretty fuckin' great so far.
The new Dominican contact
we found. it's popular.
But. uh. we're gonna
need more coke
if you wanna keep this going.
How's your cash flow?
Ah. well between
paying off the guys.
and. uh. and you. and. um.
you know. some of the supply
went for personal use.
And I'm gonna be
a little bit short
-for the next buy.
-Uh-huh.
Um. so. what
I was wondering was.
you know. if you could
just front us some cash.
including what I just gave you.
Not easy running
your own business. is it?
You gotta handle inventory.
watch your guys
like a fuckin' hawk.
I guarantee you
at least one of your guys
is stealing from you.
The only one way to learn
how to do this. Jimmy.
is to do it.
So. you're not gonna
give me any money?
No.
But I got a guy.
Ruby Stein.
He shylocks for everybody.
He's very connected.
-Oh. yeah?
-Yeah. He'll lend you the money.
Just be sure. you borrow money
from Ruby Stein...
you pay him back.
If you don't. bad things happen.
One hundred thousand dollars?
Not on your life or on the life
of my great-grandchildren.
should I ever have any.
Mr. Stein. you'll get
your money back. plus your vig.
And I'm even willing
to add 10% on top of that.
Oh. that's very generous of you.
I don't care if it's 100%.
You don't have any collateral!
You know what collateral is?
-Yes.
-Good! Then you know
-you don't have any!
-Mr. Stein.
you're the biggest
loan shark in the city.
You have the money.
Of course I've got the money.
Because I don't lend it
to Irish punks off the street
come into my office
making outrageous demands.
Sorry. fellas.
Go elsewhere.
I'm a very busy man.
I'm a decorated war veteran.
I ain't no punk.
Well. good for you.
Thank you for your service.
You're not getting
any of my money.
It's all right.
My boss is Eamon Sweeney.
Eamon Sweeney?
This money's for him?
Why isn't he here?
He. uh.
needs to stay clear
of what we're doing.
But you ask around.
you'll find out who we are.
You bet your ass I will.
It's still too much.
Okay. so...
how much would you be
willing to give us?
I tell you what.
I'll give you half.
That's... That's very kind
of you. Mr. Stein.
but that's only 50 grand.
I mean. you must
be able to do more.
Plus double my vig.
You guys are obviously getting
into a very risky business.
one that might very well
get you killed
before I get repaid.
Or I might have
to kill you myself.
Take it or leave it. fellas.
Hey. handsome.
Lookin' for fun?
Yeah. get in.
Pull into the parking lot.
Twenty for a BJ.
40 for full service.
Alice? Alice Hamilton?
What is this?
Officer Keenan.
Remember me?
Hey. hey. hey. hey.
Relax.
You're not in trouble.
I just wanna talk to you.
I'm not lookin' to bust you.
You remember?
I interviewed you
in the hospital
after your face got cut.
What do you want?
I know who did this to you.
Do you now?
Yeah.
You know how I know?
Not 'cause you told anyone.
Because I overheard
Dukey Sullivan
braggin' about it at the 596.
And I'll tell you
somethin' else.
you're not the first woman
he's raped and cut.
But maybe you could be the last.
You know why?
'Cause I'm gonna put
that fucker away for so long
he never hurts anyone again.
But I need your help.
I don't know any Dukey Sullivan.
Let me see your arm.
You're still on the junk. huh?
You sick?
Here.
I'm gonna let you get well.
You can fix.
But first. I need you
to sign something.
All right?
Good.
Bridget?
Yeah?
One sugar. no milk.
-You remembered that.
-Of course I remembered.
Only you and my ma
are crazy enough
not to drink tea with milk.
What?
It's just that...
when I asked you
to hide that weapon...
I never dreamed
you'd end up on my team.
Oh. c'mon. you...
this was part
of your plan. right?
'Cause you could have
hidden that weapon anywhere.
I have to admit.
it's a good reason to see you.
And it worked.
I'm here for only one reason.
Don't forget that.
Of course.
That's why I'm letting you
man the explosion.
So. my only concern is
civilian casualties.
That never bothered you
in London.
But this is America.
and it has bothered me
every day since.
Have you thought about
how this might play out
in the American press?
The American public
are ignorant to what happens
in Northern Ireland
every fuckin' day.
It's time they woke up.
If we're as vicious as Markham.
they may not understand
who the real villain is.
You may lose American sympathy.
Are you fuckin' committed
to this or not?
-Yeah. I am.
-Then fuck America.
I only care what
the Irish think.
When Colonel Markham is dead.
there'll be dancing
on the streets of Belfast.
Ooh. you boys
can't get enough. can you?
What can I say?
People love your stuff. Nelson.
So. we'll take another two keys.
Two keys?
That's one hundred thousand.
You see how fast I do that?
It's like I'm a math genius.
But you see. the thing is.
we only have 50 grand.
But I'm good for the other half.
Hmm. You're good
for the other half?
We have a deal set up that
would get you paid immediately.
We friends?
Sure.
I'd like to think so.
Fuck you.
I don't have no friends.
And I'm not your mami.
I'm not your papi.
I'm not your girlfriend.
So I don't lend you shit.
It's cash up front.
And if you ever ask me
to front you again...
you're never gonna see me again.
I'm sorry. I must not be
hearing you right.
'cause you got
that thick fuckin' accent.
I don't know
what you're saying. but...
but you're gonna front us
the coke. right. chico?
Don't get
fucking excited. fellas.
You're in our neighborhood now.
Hey. hey. It's all right.
It's all right.
We're just negotiating.
A word of advice.
maybe don't flash those things
in a fucking Irish bar. hm?
So. how 'bout this. Nelson?
One key for 50 grand.
I think I got the math right.
Cash business we can do.
Do you have the money?
Next time.
this one better stay home.
He's my friend. not you.
So just give us the key
and fuck off.
Fuckin' Tad.
The fuck is he?
He was supposed
to be here an hour ago.
I never liked the looks
of that fuckin' guy.
Hey! Sorry. Declan.
that's five bucks!
You didn't call it!
You gotta call the shot.
-You... You fuckin' lost!
-What you talkin' about?
-You didn't call it!
-All right. well.
when you play.
you can call the fuckin'...
Hey. hey. hey.
Shut the fuck up!
He's here.
-Well. I don't fuckin' see him.
-No. 'cause he's outside.
He's in his car.
He's fuckin' scared.
He wants to do the deal
in the fuckin' car. Jimmy.
-Oh. fuck.
-Fuckin' douchebag.
you drag his ass in here.
What. he's fuckin' strapped
in a baby seat or somethin'?
Does he have the money on him?
I don't fuckin' know.
He wouldn't get out.
-Jesus fuckin' Christ.
-Fuck's sake.
What are you fuckin' good for?
No. no. no.
you stay here. all right?
Don't want that little prick
to shit himself.
-I'd fuckin' love to see that.
-Sean.
-Yeah.
-You bring the stuff.
But you stay back
until I say so.
Fuck sakes.
All right. rack 'em up.
He's over there. Jimmy.
You stay here.
Rad Tad? Jesus.
Tad.
What the fuck are
they doing here?
It's okay.
Yeah. I'm paying them
for their time.
They won't say shit.
right. girls?
-Whatever.
-Yeah.
Is it okay
if we smoke in the car?
-No. no. It's not okay.
-Oh!
My stepdad gave me
this fuckin' car.
and I don't want
cigarette burns in it.
-Jesus fuckin' Christ.
-All right. all right!
-Calm down!
-Christ. are you serious?
I am not doing this shit
with them here.
They won't say shit.
right. girls?
-Whatever.
You know what?
Fuck this.
No. Wait a minute.
wait a minute. wait a minute.
Hey.
I got the money.
It's here. C'mon.
Let me get you the money
and then you can be on your way.
What the fuck did
you bring them for?
Honestly?
In case you tried
to rob or kill me...
then I'd have witnesses.
Then I could fuck 'em.
-Win-win. right?
-Jesus Christ.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Look. let's just...
let's just go to the trunk.
Yeah? I have it
all in the trunk.
Yeah? These...
These bitches
don't know shit
about we're talkin' about.
right. girls?
We really don't give
a fuck. okay.
Can we just party?
-Yeah. let's party.
-Come on.
The money's in the trunk.
I could use some coke though.
Well. I need to see
the stuff first.
Just open the trunk.
I'm afraid
you're gonna rip me off.
Look. I'll give you one
of the girls as a thank you.
After this. I never want
to see your fuckin' face
in this neighborhood again.
do you understand me?
Now open the goddamn trunk.
All right. All right.
-Sean?
-Yeah?
It's right here.
Right here.
Now open the fuckin' trunk!
What the fuck is this?
-Fuck.
-Hey. Jimmy.
how are you doing?
Gimme the bag.
I did everything
you asked. Mr. Gotti.
Can... Can I go now?
Yeah. go ahead.
Get the fuck outta here.
Stupid fuck.
He's a fuckin' idiot. that kid.
So. that piece of shit
works for you?
Nah. he just owes me
a shit ton of money.
Listen. Jimmy.
I could blow your fucking
brains out right here.
Or we just could be partners.
like I said.
I don't know why you're making
this shit so fuckin' hard.
I told that spic
motherfucker Nelson
that if he sells you any coke.
he's a fuckin' dead man.
So. I'm your only supplier.
When you're ready to stop
fuckin' around. come talk to me.
Jimmy. I'm sorry.
Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
How could I've been
so fuckin' stupid?
I knew. I knew
that kid was full of shit!
Why would Gotti use
that fuckin' idiot?
Because he wants me
to sell coke for him.
so he doesn't get
whacked by Castellano.
And I guess saying no
to Gotti isn't an option?
Well. it seems
he won't fuckin' let me.
And I'm only still alive
'cause that dago prick
thinks he needs me!
And I still owe Ruby Stein
a shit ton of money.
Jesus Christ. I am fucked!
Okay. um. well. just...
just borrow it from Sweeney.
And what... what. tell him
that some coked-up yuppie
fleeced me of 50 grand?
What the fuck is
he gonna think of me?
So what? He takes a profit
when you sell the stuff.
and then what.
when there's a loss?
Bridget. he told me
I had to do this on my own.
So I have to fuckin'
do this on my own!
Jimmy. he is the one
who got you into this mess.
The least that man
could do is help you out.
If I see that Tad again.
I'm gonna fuckin' kill him.
Or Gotti... maybe
I just fuckin' kill Gotti.
Yeah. that's great.
then you'll have
the entire
Italian mafia after you.
That's smart.
There has to be a way
without killing anyone.
There you go.
-There you are. Mr. Sweeney.
-Thanks. Ray.
Are you fuckin' kidding me?
Fuck sake.
Jesus Christ. you fucking
kiddin' me? Look at this shit.
Fuck's sake.
Want me to take care
of this fucker?
Let's see
what this cocksucker wants.
Don't look at my fuckin' cards.
It's alright. we already
know you're bluffing.
Think you wandered
in the wrong joint. Glenn.
You shouldn't be here.
Why not? I go wherever
the fuck I please.
You're lucky to be
fuckin' breathing.
You know that. right?
You can chalk that up
to our prior friendship.
But now it's time to go.
Well. when I'm ready.
I got some business
to attend here.
I came here to talk to Dukey.
Okay. About what?
Well. that's between me and him.
Jesus.
Glenn. don't fuck with me.
No. You fucked with me
when you made threats
towards my son.
So now...
I'm gonna put you away.
Yeah. You know.
everyone around here.
they treat you
like a fuckin' saint.
We both know
what you really are.
A past-his-prime hood
who's hoping the world'll
remember him kindly
when he goes.
The truth is...
they'll line up
to piss on your grave.
and I'll be first.
What is this?
You being a hero cop now
all of a sudden. Glenn.
'cause it's hilarious.
But I think I liked you
better when you were
-taking my fuckin' bribes.
-Yeah. well.
Those days are over.
I fuck you where you breathe.
If you were to take one
in the head
right here right now. Glenn.
I mean. I'm lookin' around...
I don't see a soul in here
who's gonna testify in court
against me or any of my crew.
Oh. yeah?
They got guns?
'Cause I got three
right here on me.
So they better be fast.
But go for it.
let's see how this shakes out.
If you like those odds. you're
a fuckin' slow learner. Glenn.
Here's what I think.
I think
you're a fuckin' failure.
and you know it.
You're a failure as a cop.
As a fuckin' father. God knows.
You're a failure as a man.
Worst punishment for you is to
let you fuckin' live with that.
For now.
Oh. no. this shit is
more than decent.
It's gotta be at least 55% pure.
I don't know what the fuck
is the matter with
those Irish punks.
They didn't even try
-to rip you off.
-Yeah. so...
we're good now?
You know? I can go?
You owe my bookie
a quarter of a million dollars.
You ain't going nowhere.
Yeah. but you...
but you said that.
if I get you the coke.
that you can cut it.
and you could sell it
for half a million
-and that we'd be even.
-Yeah.
-Like. we'd be more than even!
-Listen. Tad.
you know what your problem is?
You're a degenerate gambler.
You don't know when to stop.
I'm never gonna gamble again.
-Bullshit.
-Yeah. I mean. he should know.
See. Johnny here is
a gambler too.
Fuck yourself.
Listen. Tad...
getting me this key
ain't gonna do it.
All right?
I gotta do a lotta legwork
before I get my money back.
you understand?
I gotta sell all this shit.
Yeah. well.
I'd love to stay and help.
but I...
I really should
get out of town.
You know. those Irish punks are
gonna come looking for me so...
You're damn right they are.
Sit down.
What?
I said. sit the fuck down.
What're you doing?
I did everything you asked!
Yeah. but now I got
two things that the Irish want.
Right? I got cocaine.
And I got you.
Good man.
See it
coming through now. Donal?
-Yeah. I got it there.
-Got it?
-Yup.
-Careful. careful.
-All right.
-Yeah.
Two more coming through. Donal.
-Got it?
Yep.
Come on.
All right. blasting cap is set.
-Good?
-Thank you.
Come on.
-Yeah?
-She's loaded and ready.
You're gonna have to flip
the red toggle to on.
You'll feel it click
under your thumb.
-Mm-hmm.
-That arms the signal.
Then press the black button.
Hold it down
for two full seconds.
-Well. what if it doesn't work?
-It will.
So don't press it just yet.
Logan and I have
been scouting the location.
There are several
backup places we could park
if the hydrant is blocked.
We timed the street
for meter maids.
They make rounds
at least three times a day.
Registration
and everything else in order?
-It is.
-Right.
Now. we just gotta pick
someone to go with Bridget.
Oh no. No. no. no.
I can do this on my own.
-We need a backup. just in case.
-In case what?
-I'm more than happy.
-I'd like to make
that bastard fry.
Two women will be
less suspicious.
You okay with that?
In case what?
In case you get cold feet.
You're on.
After he raped me.
he cut me and threatened
to burn me alive.
The more I cried.
the more he cut in to me.
Man is a fuckin' monster.
Yes. he is.
She signed an affidavit.
That's enough to get
an arrest warrant
for Dukey Sullivan.
Yeah. sure is.
But how is that gonna help
make Eamon Sweeney flip?
Dukey has a rap sheet
as long as the Holland Tunnel.
Been partners
with Sweeney for years.
He knows where
the bodies are buried.
And he ain't loyal
like Eddie Breen.
That weasel-dick motherfucker
will sing in a minute.
So. who am I talking to?
The cop on the take.
or the one who won
all those awards years ago?
Oh. I don't know.
You bring out the best in me.
What can I say?
I just don't get it.
How'd you fall so far?
What happened to you?
I'm gonna tell you something
that isn't in my file.
My wife and I had
a second child.
baby was stillborn.
My wife started
using drugs again.
I couldn't deal with it.
so I left.
She OD'd and died.
After that...
I stopped caring.
But now. I got my head
screwed on right.
I wanna trust you.
You'll bring Dukey in
to testify.
and not for revenge. right?
Just get me the warrant.
You need more time. huh?
Just... Just give us
another week.
and... and you'll get
your money back. I promise you.
This may come
as a surprise to you boys.
but I've heard this before.
I'm sure you have.
but you can trust us. Mr. Stein.
And I've heard that before too.
Look. how about you shut
the fuck up. or maybe
-we don't pay you at all?
-Mickey!
-Fuck this guy!
-And I've heard that
before. too.
What's the matter with you?
Are you stupid?
What is it. I look meek to you?
I sit behind this little desk
with my little suit.
You know. where's my army?
Where's my guns?
He's so vulnerable.
such an easy target.
Let me tell you something.
My customers are
some of the most dangerous men
on this planet!
They have a vested interest
in my well-being!
Why? Because I'm the bank!
You harm me. and you're signing
your own death warrants.
you hear me?
Of this. you can be assured!
That's why I don't need
to walk around carrying a gun.
be a tough guy.
So. spare me your threats.
Let me ask you something.
This cocaine business is
very lucrative.
What in the flying
fuck happened?
The fucking guineas is
what happened. Stein.
I'm asking him!
John Gotti set us up.
because he wants us
to sell for him.
So why don't you?
'Cause we're Irish.
and he's a fuckin'
Italian piece of shit.
I'm half Lithuanian
and half Russian.
Which half should I hate?
This is America.
the melting pot!
What's the matter with you?
Would you stop thinking about
where your grandparents fucked.
start thinking
about making a little money!
We can't sell
for John fuckin' Gotti.
Why not?
I know Gotti. I know Castellano.
I know your boss. too.
I know all the bosses.
they got one thing in common.
They're greedy.
and they're hypocrites.
You think Paul doesn't get
kick-ups from Gotti.
with all that extra drug money?
Am I wrong in thinking that
Sweeney gets kick-ups from you?
Huh?
All right. all right. all right.
Do what you want.
Pay me back. don't pay me back.
but if you don't pay me back.
I'm gonna have you both killed.
I can do it right now.
But I'd rather have my money
than shed blood.
You got to know
when to kill in this business.
So. do yourselves a favor.
do us all a favor.
and think about Gotti's offer.
You gonna pay me.
you fuckin' asshole!
Huh? Huh?
Right now.
-That's right.
-Let him go.
I said let him go. you fuck.
You.
Get the fuck outta here.
Fuckin' Glenn Keenan.
Hello. Dukey.
I'm doing business.
I got a warrant for your arrest.
-It's legit.
-For what. Mr. Rat Cop?
What does it matter?
I'm takin' you in.
You gonna come like a gentleman?
Whatever it is. it won't stick.
Sweeney's got the best
fuckin' lawyers in the city.
So go ahead.
-You gonna cuff me?
-Fuck that.
I'm gonna tune you up first.
Okay. tough guy.
-Really?
-Just us.
Let's do this.
One on one? Man to man?
You sure you don't want
to call your friends.
you fuckin' little
ginger monkey? C'mon.
Huh?
Come on.
Here. might help you out.
You motherfucker.
You fuckin' mutt.
You wanna piss on me?
Okay. there's the consulate.
It's almost 1:00 PM.
He should be walking
out of that building any minute.
-This is exciting.
-Exciting?
Is this a game to you?
Shut the fuck up. Mary.
No peace prize for murderers!
Free Ireland!
Markham. go home!
-Markham. go home!
-Fuck.
Oh. my God.
What the hell
are they doin' here?
This is not...
This is not good.
They're Mothers
of Irish Freedom.
they... they are mothers
who have lost family
to the cause.
Shit.
They're here for Markham too.
Fuck.
Oh. shit.
This is bad. Okay.
Let me think. let me think.
Die!
No peace prize for murderers!
Wait. There he is.
That's him.
Do it!
Push the button!
-Push the button!
-Wait. wait.
Do it!
Free Ireland!
I can't.
Kids died!
Hey. fellas.
Good to see you boys.
You guys want some coffee.
make you a little espresso?
-No. thanks.
-You're a whiskey man. right?
Yeah. that's right.
Come on in.
I don't have
any of that Irish shit.
so you'll have
to settle for bourbon.
What the fuck is that for?
Oh. these?
They're for my stomach.
So I can talk to Italians
without gettin' sick.
Fuckin' racist. this kid. huh?
You boys want your coke back?
Ready to talk terms?
Good.
I'll take 80 percent.
you keep 20.
Cut this five ways to Sunday.
you'll still triple your money.
Fifty. fifty. like you said.
Do I look like
an asshole to you. Jimmy?
That ship has sailed.
But I'll go 75. 25.
or you can get nothing.
And what about Sweeney?
He can't ever find out
we're doin' this.
And neither can Big Paul.
We're in the same fuckin' boat.
Those two can suck
each others' dicks.
-We got a deal?
-All right. but just
so we're clear.
you supply. we sell.
then you get your cut.
Maybe this kid isn't
as crazy as he seems.
All right. I'll cover.
Then we have a deal.
Yeah. there's just
one more thing.
Yeah. if you're
gonna sell for me.
it can't get out
that some piece of shit
yuppie dickhead robbed you.
Come on.
You gotta end him.
There's no need to kill him.
We have a deal now.
Just let him go.
Well. he's gonna die either way.
Ain't that right. Tad?
If I do it.
then we don't have a deal.
and if you do it. we're good.
It's not necessary.
Do you want the fucking deal
or not. Jimmy?
Yeah. We do.
Congratulations.
We have a deal.
You know. you got
a good friend there.
You can learn from him.
♪ Keep your back up
against the wall. hey! ♪
♪ Back up against the wall ♪
♪ Keep your back up
against the wall. hey! ♪
♪ Standing on ground
we won't back down ♪
♪ We march into the night ♪
♪ Storms roll in.
the hate begins ♪
♪ But we're rising
to survive ♪
♪ The dark within.
the terrible sin ♪
♪ So we strike
with all our might ♪
♪ The blood runs hot
as we all just fight ♪
♪ We'll never
lose the light ♪
♪ Keep your back up
against the wall. hey! ♪
♪ Back up against the wall ♪
♪ Keep your back up
against the wall. hey! ♪
♪ The drums will sound
as we hold our ground ♪
♪ For the courage
starts to burn ♪
♪ Through the blood
and the rain ♪
♪ And the loss and the pain ♪
♪ There's nothing
we won't turn ♪
♪ The leveling we draw is
the only law ♪
♪ And the cowards
never learn ♪
♪ The strugglers fall
in the wake and crawl ♪
♪ So we will never adjourn ♪
♪ Keep your back up
against the wall. hey! ♪
against the wall ♪
♪ And we're still here
while the whole world burns ♪
♪ Keep your back up
against the wall ♪
♪ And we're still here ♪
♪ While the whole world ♪
♪ Burns ♪
Subtitling: difuze